<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Kedar Karpe - misc</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/misc.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2017-08-02T20:00:00+05:30</updated><entry><title>Summer 2017</title><link href="/summer-2017.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-08-02T20:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-08-02T20:00:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Kedar Prasad Karpe</name></author><id>tag:None,2017-08-02:/summer-2017.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;6 hours to my flight and I still hadn't received my visa! Today sitting at the Munich International Airport I wonder how the summer of 2017 would have been if the visa wouldn't have arrived on time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spent the last 6 weeks working with ARS Control Laboratory at University …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;6 hours to my flight and I still hadn't received my visa! Today sitting at the Munich International Airport I wonder how the summer of 2017 would have been if the visa wouldn't have arrived on time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spent the last 6 weeks working with ARS Control Laboratory at University of Modena and Reggio Emilia. My supervisor and guide Dr. Lorenzo Sabattini is an Assistant Professor at the Department of Science and Methods of Engineering at the university. He also co-chairs the IEEE Technical Committee on Multi-Robot Systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align="center" style="position:static; height: 100%; width: 100%; top:0;left 0;"&gt;
&lt;img style=" float:centre; "  src="images/tecnopolo.jpg" width=100%  title="Visit Computer Hope" / &gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During my duration of stay, the research included implementation of a decentralized state estimator scheme for multi-robot systems and further analysis of its robustness to multiple system conditions and experimental noise or errors. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The decentralized state estimation scheme was designed to estimate the state of a network only using certain nodes, termed as the independent nodes. These independent nodes compute the input to the network in a decentralized manner, that is, based only on locally available knowledge, to achieve a collective goal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Code available on: &lt;a href="https://github.com/karpenet/Decentralized-State-Estimation"&gt;https://github.com/karpenet/Decentralized-State-Estimation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I must say Italy is a beautiful country. From aesthetic the city centres and Italian piazzas to the delectable Italian cuisine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While on the weekends, I spent most of my time visiting nearby attractions. The opulent factory of Pagani Automobili and the Enzo Ferrari Museum are now checked off my bucket list! Though I really wished I could visit Automobili Lamborghini.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align="center" style="position:static; height: 100%; width: 100%; top:0;left 0;"&gt;
&lt;img style=" float:centre; "  src="images/pagani.jpg" height="200"  title="Visit Computer Hope" / &gt;
&lt;img style=" float:centre;"   src="images/ferrari.jpg"  height="200" /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another weekend was spent trekking through Cinque Terre, a UNESCO World Heritage Site in the Liguria region of Italy. Rugged landscape overlooking the beautiful coast of the Italian Riviera makes this destination a must visit. Also equivalently famous is the seafood!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div align="center" style="position:static; height: 100%; width: 100%; top:0;left 0;"&gt;
&lt;img style=" float:centre; "  src="images/manarola.jpg" height="200"  /&gt;
&lt;img style=" float:centre;"   src="images/laspezia.jpg"  height="200" /&gt;
&lt;img style=" float:centre;"   src="images/riomaggiore.jpg"  height="200" /&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was lucky enough to have a great Airbnb host who introduced us to Notte Rossa (a local cultural happening), took us to the apertivo and also cooked us meals almost every single day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now as the boarding time approaches, yet another great summer comes to a conclusion!&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>First Post</title><link href="/first-post.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-05-15T20:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2016-05-15T20:00:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Kedar Prasad Karpe</name></author><id>tag:None,2016-05-15:/first-post.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is my first post on the blog. This blog will be about my endeavors in electronics, spanning from embedded systems to swarm robotics. At present I would be posting my project logs on this website, in future I plan to create tutorials on this page. The jargon used has …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is my first post on the blog. This blog will be about my endeavors in electronics, spanning from embedded systems to swarm robotics. At present I would be posting my project logs on this website, in future I plan to create tutorials on this page. The jargon used has been made noob friendly, if you still have any questions, feel free to contact me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For most of my microcontroller/microprocessor based projects, I intend use the AVR (of course from Atmel!) and ARM (mostly from ST Microelectronics). All the softwares used are Mac OS friendly, you may also use Windows alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the projects are Open-Source and the relevant files can be found on Github. This blog is created using Pelican, which is a Python based framework.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy Making!&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry></feed>